{
    "question": "Contoh dialog expression suggestion?",
    "attachments": [],
    "answers": [
        {
            "answer": "I have been usiung asparagus extract ( 2capsules per day in the morning ) on the suggestion of my doctor who is aDO.<br>This has helped reduce the amount of fluid retention. Seacoast vitamins has consistently had the lowest price for the same brand I was buying at the heralthfood store.",
            "attachments": []
        }
    ],
    "related_questions": [
        {
            "slug": "aku-belum-mengerti-dengan-jelas-tentang-past-perfect-tense-523",
            "question": "Aku belum mengerti dengan jelas tentang past perfect tense.",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "The PAST PERFECT TENSE indicates that an action was completed (finished or \"perfected\") at some point in the past before something else happened. This tense is formed with the past tense form of \"to have\" (HAD) plus the past participle of the verb (which can be either regular or irregular in form):\n    I had walked two miles by lunchtime. \n    I had run three other marathons before entering the Boston Marathon .",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "<span>ita menggunakan Past Perfect (simple) tense untuk menunjukkan suatu tindakan di masa lalu berkaitan dengan tindakan lain sebelumnya di masa lalu. Bisa juga\u00a0pengertian Past perfect tensedigunakan utuk menjelaskan kalau sesuatu terjadi saat sebelum waktu spesifik.</span>Penggunaan Past Perfect Tense1. menceritakan sebuah tindakan yang sudah selesai sebelum tindakan lain di masa laluRumus = had + past participleContoh:<span>a.You had studied math before you moved to los angeles.<br>Kamu sudah belajar matematika sebelum pindah ke los angeles<br>b. You had not studied math before you moved to Los angeles.<br>Kamu belum belajar matematika sebelum pindah ke los angeles<br>c. Had you studied math before you moved to los angeles?<br>Apakah kamu sudah belajar matematika sebelum ke los angeles?<br>2. kalimat pengandaian (Conditional Sentence) Type III</span><span>If + subject + Past perfect + would have + verb III<br>If we had known the answer, we would have told you<br>Seandainya kami telah tahu jawabannya, kami akan telah mengatakan padamu (kenyataanya kami sudah tidak tahu jawabannya)</span><span>3. kalimat tak langsung (reported speech)<br>Reported speech adalah kalimat yang digunakan untuk menjelaskan perkataan seseorang. Kalimat ini mengubah dialog menjadi kalimat biasa<br>Ann: I have searched all the rooms.<br>George: Ann said she had searched all the rooms.<br>George : Ann mengatakan bahwa dia sudah mencari semua kamar</span>untuk pembahasan selengkapnya tentang reported speech dalam berbagai tenses disini3 Rumus Past Perfect Tense<span>\u2022 Positif (+)<br>Subject + had + verb III + (past participle) + object<br>\u2022 Negatif (-)<br>Subject + had + not + verb III + object<br>\u2022 Tanya (?)<br>Had + subject + verb III + object ?</span>Contoh kalimat \u2013 Past Perfect tense:<span>They had been here before 1945 (+)<br>- mereka telah berada disini sebelum tahun 1945<br>They had not been here before 1945 (-)<br>- mereka belum berada disini sebelum tahun 1945<br>Had they been here before 1945 ? (?)<br>- apakah mereka telah berada disini sebelum 1945 ?</span><span>She had gone to Amsterdam when I called her (+)<br>- dia telah pergi ke Amsterdam ketika aku meneleponnya<br>She had not gone to Amsterdam when I called her (-)<br>- dia belum pergi ke Amsterdam ketika aku meneleponnya<br>Had she gone to Amsterdam when you called her ?<br>- apakah dia telah pergi ke Amsterdam ketika kamu meneleponnya ?</span><span>Keterangan waktu (Adverb of time) yang umum digunakan dalam\u00a0past Perfect tense:<br>after, before, already, as soon as, just, yet, until, till, by the time that.</span><span>Past Perfect tense\u00a0juga digunakan untuk ungkapan seperti : \u201cI wish\u201d, \u201cas if/though\u201d and \u201cif only\u201d.</span><span>\u2022 I wish I hadn\u2019t gone there ( aku berharap aku tidak pernah pergi kesana )<br>\u2022 Jono looked as if he had done something terrible. ( Jono tampak seolah-olah ia telah melakukan sesuatu yang mengerikan )</span>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "arrange-the-jumbled-words-to-form-meaningful-sentencesstarting-w-193",
            "question": "arrange the jumbled words to form meaningful sentences,starting with the underlined words. 1. phone-puppet-his-invite-the-I-number-my-see-Finto-know-will-if-show-to-I-at-place 2. and-holiday-Bali-if-have-will-his-Lombok-long-go-year-Mr. Kukuh-family-to-they-and-this-a \u00a0 mohon di bantu",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "2. Mr. Kukuh and his family will go to Bali and Lombok if they have a long holiday this year<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "ubah-kalimat-tersebut-ke-dalam-bentuk-pasif-1-it-is-said-that-ma-237",
            "question": "Ubah kalimat tersebut ke dalam bentuk pasif    1. It is said that many people are homeless after floods\r\n2. People say that Arthur is very rich\r\n3. People say that he has 22 children\u00a0",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "1. It is said that many people are homeless after floods<br>-- ini udah pasif ya?\u00a0<br>Many people are homeless due to flood, it is said by the newspaper<br><br>2. People say that Arthur is very rich<br>Arthur is very rich, is said by people<br><span><br>3. People say that he has 22 children\u00a0<br>he has 22 children, is said by people\u00a0<br><br></span>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "bagaimanakah-penggunaan-kata-either-720",
            "question": "Bagaimanakah penggunaan kata 'either'?",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<span>untuk 2 kalimat yang sama-sama negative (-). Contoh dengan<span> (tenses 1) simple present tense, menggunakan </span></span><span><span>katakerja be (am, are is) dengan </span>katasifat (adjective) fine /fain/ = baik.</span><br>example:<br>you are not fine and i am not, either<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "untuk 2 kalimat sama-sama negative dengan menggunakan kata kerja be(am,are,is)<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "pengertian-dan-contoh-adverb-of-frequency-256",
            "question": "Pengertian dan contoh adverb of frequency",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "adverb yang menggambarkan frekuensi seseorang melakukan suatu pekerjaan, misalnya setiap hari, atau beberapa kali dalam 1 bulan<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "pengertian\u00a0: kata keterangan yang menyatakan seberapa sering suatu kegiatan yang dilakukan.",
                    "attachments": [
                        "answer-attachments/pengertian-dan-contoh-adverb-of-frequency-256-1.gif"
                    ]
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "tolong-describe-dengan-tema-my-beloved-home-523",
            "question": "Tolong describe dengan tema \"my beloved home\"",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "I live in an ordinary house, but I always feel that I belong here for no reason. My house really cozy, it has 4 rooms with AC inside, 1 kitchen, 3 bathrooms, 1 livingrooms, and a green garden in front of it. My mom always take care of this house. I think it&#039;s right that our house is our palace because we can do what we want no matter what. Two years ago, I almost moved to the other house because there was an accident, and sssttt I can&#039;t tell you, because it&#039;s secret. So I think that&#039;s all",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "did-he-has-a-bad-seat-203",
            "question": "Did he has a bad seat?",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "dia memiliki kursi yang buruk?",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Ini merupakan idiom dari suatu kondisi yang kurang nyaman pada perusahaan<br>contoh lain adalah\u00a0<br>His job is kind of hand wringing profession.<br>Pekerjaan dia adalah pekerjaan yang kadang meremas dirinya.\u00a0",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "apa-keegunaan-dari-whowhosewhomwhichwhere-dalam-adjective-cla-586",
            "question": "apa keegunaan dari who,whose,whom,which,where dalam adjective clause, saya agak kurang mengerti sepenuhnya ?",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Who\u00a0=\u00a0( Sentences + Adjective Clause + Auxilary/Verb\u00a0) Untuk Subject<br>\u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0Ex:\u00a0<strong>I saw the man <u>who is </u>tall<br>\u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0Is =</strong> Auxilary<br><br>Whom =\u00a0( Sentences + Adjective Clause + Subject ) Untuk Subject<u><br></u> \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 Ex:\u00a0<strong>The woman <u>whom you</u> saw last night is my sister<br></strong>\u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0<strong>You =\u00a0</strong>Subject<br><br>Whose = ( Sentences + Adjective Clause + Noun ) Untuk Subject<br>\u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0Ex:\u00a0<strong>Santi <u>whose hair</u> is black and lock is beautiful<br></strong><strong>\u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0Hair =\u00a0</strong>Noun<br><br>Which = ( Sentences + Adjective Clause + Aux/S/Verb ) Untuk Object<br>\u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0Ex:\u00a0<strong>The food <u>which is</u> made of bread and sausage is hot dog<br>\u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0The cat <u>which sultan</u> feeds every morning is very funny<br>\u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0Is =\u00a0</strong>Auxilary<br>\u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0\u00a0<strong> Sultan =\u00a0</strong>Subject<br><br>Where = Untuk menjelaskan tempat<br>\u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0Ex:\u00a0<strong>Mall, where we shopping is aweso</strong><strong>me<br></strong><strong><br></strong>Semoga bermanfaat :)\u00a0<br><strong></strong>Jika ingin bertanya, silahkan komen dibawah :)<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "choose-the-inappropriate-structure-in-the-following-sentences-rim-675",
            "question": "Choose the inappropriate structure in the following sentences    rima : they said the exam was complicated. Do You think so ?\r\nAmi : I Disagree with you. You can see that everyone's score is satisfied.",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "rima : they\u00a0<u>said\u00a0</u><span>the exam complicated. Did\u00a0You\u00a0</span><u>think\u00a0</u>so ?<br><span>Ami : I\u00a0was\u00a0</span><u>Disagree</u><span>\u00a0with you. You can saw that everyone&#039;s score was\u00a0</span><u>satisfied.</u>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "rima : they\u00a0<u>said\u00a0</u>the exam complicated. Did\u00a0You\u00a0<u>think\u00a0</u>so ?<br>Ami : I\u00a0was\u00a0<u>Disagree</u>\u00a0with you. You can saw that everyone&#039;s score was\u00a0<u>satisfied.</u>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "buat-kalimat-pujian-responnya-tentang-memuji-keindahan-alam-me-326",
            "question": "buat kalimat pujian + responnya tentang memuji keindahan alam, memuji mother, father, granpa/ma, teacher, brother and sister, friend, best friend pet, your self",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Me : Mom, you are so beautiful in this night.\nMom : really? You never told me before mommy use beauty fash.\nMe : yes mom, you are A princess for daddy tonight, let tell Daddy, if Daddy shock, ask A opinion about you mom.\nMom : Ok , thankyou my sweetheart, i love you.",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}